## Ting Pan

## UX Engineer / Front End Developer / UX Designer

HCl student with passion and experience in design and development. Being enthusiastic about learning new stuff like VR, data analysis, and machine learning, I can quickly digest new knowledge, discovery new technology opportunities, and apply them in design and development process.

#### **Education**

Master of Science in Information Studies, The University of Texas at Austin 2018-08 present • Graduate Research Assistant with Dr. Jakki Bailey in Virtual Reality Lab. • Related courses: Algorithms, Introduction to Machine Learning, Information Retrieval, Advanced Design for Artificial Intelligence, Designing User Interfaces for Children. **Bachelor of Architecture, China University of Mining and Technology** 2013-09 -2018-06 • Study-abroad scholarship, awarded by China Scholarship Council. • Outstanding student, and the 1st/2nd Prize Merit-Based Scholarship. 2016-07 -**Exchange Student, University of Western Australia** 2016-12 • Completed comics project and sculpture installation.

## **Experience**

Experience		
2019-01 -	Graduate Research Assistant in Virtual Reality Lab	
present	Take charge of 3D modeling and animation.	
	<ul> <li>Develop VR game for children in Unity environment using C#.</li> </ul>	
	<ul> <li>Research on people's attitudes towards auto-generated avatars.</li> </ul>	
2018-12 - Frontend Developer in CHINA GATHERING @ SXSW		
2019-03	Helped with media pitch, guest interview for ChinaGathering @ SXSW 2019.	
	Conducted website development as lead developer.	
	<ul> <li>Participated in the interview and press release writing of Alibaba group.</li> </ul>	
Droinct		

# Project

2019-03 - 2019-05	<ul> <li>Painting GO! - Machine learning product demo (Course Project)</li> <li>Trained the machine learning model of painting style classification, deployed it using Python Flask, and created a fully-functioned website for the product.</li> <li>Received Best Project Award by Popular Vote in the final presentation.</li> </ul>
2019-01 - Farmvision - Al Product Prototyping (Course Project)	
2019-05	<ul> <li>Provided insights for AI opportunities, applied design thinking to the application prototyping, and composed storytelling for final presentation.</li> </ul>
2018-12 -	Data Visualization Project for IEEE Pacific Visualization 2019 Competition
2019-03	<ul> <li>Analyzed food nutrition data; developed a website to present food story and data visualization; and built interactive functions using JavaScript.</li> </ul>
2018-10 -	Spatial Exploration – AR Game for Children Education (Course Project)
2018-11	<ul> <li>Designed the game content and interface independently; wrote a paper to scientifically explain design strategy.</li> </ul>
2018-09 -	Austin Animal Adoption Website (Course Project)
2018-11	<ul> <li>Used Python Flask to build the database and website framework; applied CNN</li> </ul>

model to extract animal feature.

## **Personal Info**

#### **Address**

3600 N Hills Dr APT250 Austin, TX78731

#### **Phone**

+1 737 333 9769

#### E-mail

ting.pan@utexas.edu

#### **Personal Website**

http://tingpan.work

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ting-pan-546283155

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/ CCCCChloe

## **Coding Skills**

Python
Java
HTML5
CSS3
JavaScript
Library (Bootstrap, React.js, jQuery)
C#
Git

## **Design Skills**

User Interface Design
Prototyping
Storytelling
Information Architecture
Data visualization

### **Software**

Joittvare			
Unity	••••		
3ds Max	••••		
Rhinoceros	••••		
V-Ray	••••		
Photoshop	••••		
Illustrator	••••		
Premiere	••••		